sftravel.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy SFTRAVEL

**_Privacy Policy_**

Our business name is **SFTRAVEL, LLC (hereafter “SFTRAVEL” or “Company”)**. We are the owner of the trademark and web site [www.SFTRAVEL.com](http://www.sftravel.com/) **®** , as well as other web sites located on the Internet. All information provided in this Privacy Policy pertains to **SFTRAVEL, LLC,** [www.SFTRAVEL.com](http://www.sftravel.com/) **®** (hereafter “web site”) **** and our other web sites, either existing now or created in the future. SFTRAVEL provides a collection of online resources, including classified listings, advertising, email services and links to third party web sites (hereafter "Services")

**_I. General_**

A. SFTRAVEL takes User privacy seriously and takes reasonable efforts to protect it. We have created this Privacy Policy (hereafter “Policies”) in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. **AS MORE CLEARLY DEFINED HEREIN, WE WILL NEVER KNOWINGLY SELL OR ASSIGN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITHOUT YOUR KNOWLEDGE AND OR APPROVAL.** **Please read these Policies carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information described below.**

B.  These Policies apply to all the web sites owned by SFTRAVEL. Since these are developing web sites, and because Internet technologies are constantly evolving, these Policies are subject to change at any time and any changes will be posted on this page. 

C. These Policies work hand-in-hand with our Terms and Conditions of Use, found elsewhere on the SFTRAVEL web sites.

_II. Definitions_

The following words used in these Policies shall have the following meanings:

            1\. " _Personal Information_ " shall mean all data and/or information provided by, and about, User.

            2\. "SFTRAVEL web sites" shall mean all web sites on which **SFTRAVEL** provides products and/or Services.

            3\. "SFTRAVEL User" shall mean all Users of the SFTRAVEL **web sites.**

      4. "SFTRAVEL Products and Services" shall mean all products and/or Services provided directly by **SFTRAVEL.**

**_III. What Personally Identifiable Information Does SFTRAVEL Collect and How Is It Used?_**

A.  In order to use the Services provided by SFTRAVEL, you will be asked for certain personally identifiable information such as name, email address, home or business address, credit card and other information. _For example_ , when you request information on our services, contact information you provide to us can be used to communicate with you. 

B.  SFTRAVEL will not collect personally identifiable information from Users while they use our web sites unless they voluntarily provide it to us or authorize us to collect such information. _For example,_ if you purchase products or Services, you will be required to provide information to complete the purchasing transaction.

C. Users may provide other information about themselves, in addition to the mandatory Personal Information (hereafter “Voluntary Information _"_ ). 

D. Users’ Voluntary Information provided to SFTRAVEL will be viewable to SFTRAVEL, as well as its partners and vendors. 

E. SFTRAVEL may use or disclose User’s personally identifiable information to:

            1\. Operate and manage the SFTRAVEL web sites;

            2\. Provide products/Services that have been requested by you; or

            3\. Respond to other inquires or requests by you. 

            4\. Provide you with information about specials, sales or new products        or Services that SFTRAVEL will have in the future.

            5.  It’s partners and/or vendors in order to fulfill orders and/or quote             requests.

F. In order to provide the best services to Users, SFTRAVEL may disclose User name on certain pages at [www.SFTRAVEL.com](http://www.sftravel.com/) **®**. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in the establishment or exercise of legal rights or defenses against legal claims, to comply with applicable laws or regulations, to comply with a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of our Terms and Conditions  of Use. We will never sell User Information to any 3rd-party not affiliated with SFTRAVEL, without consent, except in connection with the sale or merger of SFTRAVEL or the division responsible for such services provided.

G. SFTRAVEL may also use such Voluntary Information for marketing its products and services to you **_unless_** you have ‘opted out’ of receiving such marketing information from us. User may ‘opt out’ by checking their Account Settings.

H. SFTRAVEL may, from time to time, send or post surveys or requests for User Feedback in order to help us make our web site and services better. Any responses we receive from Users will be used only to evaluate our web sites and Services and no personally identifiable information from respondents will be shared with any non-employees of SFTRAVEL. 

I. SFTRAVEL may, from time to time, send notices about special offers, promotions or contests. If you sign up to participate in any of these, we will collect your email address. If you are chosen for a promotion or as a winner in a contest, you give SFTRAVEL permission to use your name, image and other information about you, for marketing purposes.

**_IV._** _ What Non-Personally Identifiable Information Does SFTRAVEL Collect and How Is It Used?_

A.  SFTRAVEL collects and tracks certain non-personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, IP numbers and browser type, access times, domain names, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual. 

B. SFTRAVEL may use and disclose non-personally identifiable information for any number of reasons, including but not limited to, working with business partners and improving our web site and services.

_V. Does SFTRAVEL Have A Newsletter?_

A.  SFTRAVEL regularly sends out newsletters by emails (collectively, hereinafter, referred to as the "Newsletter") to all SFTRAVEL Users (unless they have ‘opted-out’). In these Newsletters, we may inform you about new features from SFTRAVEL and about the upcoming week’s events or special promotions. 

B.  You may choose to unsubscribe from the Newsletter at any time by sending an email to the link provided at the end of each Newsletter or by checking your Account Settings.

**_VI._** _**Does SFTRAVEL Use** Cookies and Logs?_

A. Cookies are small text files that a web site can write to your computer. SFTRAVEL, like many other web sites, may use cookies to identify you, customize web page content and allow you to log in once to our web sites and search or post without having to log in again. If you reached our web sites by clicking on a link or advertisement on another web site, then we also log that information. This helps us to maximize our Internet exposure, and to understand the interests of our Users. Cookies cannot be used to read data off of your hard drive, and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other web sites.

B.  Cookies are also used by our affiliates to identify you as a User of SFTRAVEL.

C.  SFTRAVEL does not use cookies to store information such as credit card numbers, telephone numbers, or other information you provide, unless you register as a Member. To maintain your privacy, you can disable your browser's ability to accept cookies. Although you may do so, you may find that your browser reacts strangely when visiting not only our web sites, but other web sites as well

D. Our advertisers and 3rd-party partners may use cookies on the SFTRAVEL web site or an external web site. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies _,_ hence, we will not be responsible for their use or misuse.

E.  This Policy only covers the use of cookies by SFTRAVEL. It does not cover the use of cookies by any other 3rd-party or advertiser.

F.  Like many other web sites, [www.SFTRAVEL.com](http://www.sftravel.com/) **®,** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and number of clicks that we use to analyze trends, administer the web site, track User’s movement around the web site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

_VII. Is My Information Private With SFTRAVEL’S Merchants and Advertisers?_

A. The SFTRAVEL web sites may contain links to various 3rd-party web sites and the external web sites of our advertisers and/or 3rd-party partners. Each of these web sites may have a Privacy Policy that differs from that of SFTRAVEL. This Policy does not cover the Privacy Policies of other web sites. We urge you to check the Privacy Policies of each web site that you may visit or interact with.

B.  The only information that may be shared between SFTRAVEL and one of our partner web sites is that which pertains to information used in the furtherance of tracking an order and providing Users with correct information regarding same.

C.  Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to SFTRAVEL, affiliate merchants and 3rd-party affiliate program management companies, for accurate tracking purposes. SFTRAVEL will not release this information to other parties unless you request it. ** _VIII. What About Data Security?_**

A.  SFTRAVEL has instituted appropriate security measures that protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from Users. 

B.  SFTRAVEL requires that our advertisers and partners ensure the security of the data that Users provide to them, however, in the event of a breach of their security measures, User agrees that SFTRAVEL will not be liable for any loss or damage to you.

C.  SFTRAVEL limits access to personal information about Users to employees for whom we reasonably believe it is necessary, in order to provide products or Services. 

D. SFTRAVEL has physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with international regulations to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our web site.

**_IX. May I See the Information SFTRAVEL Collects About Me?_** __

_Yes!_ We provide Users with access to Personal Information, account status, contact information (i.e., name, address, telephone number, etc.) and other information that you may upload to our web site. Users may access the information by logging into the web site or by sending an email to [Customer Support via this form](http://sftravel.com/blog/contact-us).  We will respond within 24 hours.

**_X._** _**Can I** **Opt** -out?_

A. SFTRAVEL gives you the option to remove your personally identifiable information from our list of active Users. 

B. You may also choose to opt-out of certain communications from SFTRAVEL, such as our Newsletter.

C. All requests for unsubscribing or opting-out should be made by sending an email to [Customer Support with this form](http://sftravel.com/blog/contact-us). We will respond within 24 hours. 

D.  SFTRAVEL is not responsible for removing your personally identifiable information from the lists of any 3rd-party partner or advertiser who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this Policy.

**_XI._** _**Where Is The** **Web Site** **Located?**_

SFTRAVEL web sites are maintained in the State of Nevada, USA. If User is located outside of the USA, by using any of our web sites, User authorizes the import of information and its use as specified in these Policies. _XII. What Is The Minimum Age To Use SFTRAVEL’S Web Site?_

A.  Use of the SFTRAVEL web sites and products/Services are intended for persons who are eighteen (18) years or older. 

B.  If proof comes to the attention of SFTRAVEL that a User is under the age of eighteen (18) years, and is accessing our Services and/or products without the consent, approval or authorization of their parents or legal guardian, SFTRAVEL will immediately terminate such service. 

_XIII. Will There Be Changes To This Privacy Policy?_

A. SFTRAVEL reserves the right to amend or revise these Policies at any time, in the event that this becomes necessary after their initial release, or in the event that it becomes necessary with respect to additional or amended services provided by SFTRAVEL. 

B. SFTRAVEL will not personally notify you of any amendments or revisions to these Policies. **Users are urged to check these _Policies_ frequently in order to determine whether any changes have been made. Users understand and agree that continued use of the SFTRAVEL web sites assumes that they have read and accepted these Policies _,_ as may be amended from time to time.**

_XIV. Where Can I Access These Policies?_

These Policies are accessible from the Home Page of the SFTRAVEL web site, under the link “Privacy Policy _.”_

**_XV. Spy ware_**

SFTRAVEL never uses or installs spy ware on your computer, nor do we use spy ware to retrieve information from your computer.

**_XVI. Your California Privacy Rights_**

California has passed legislation requiring certain specific disclosures be made available to California residents who use the Internet and provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. That legislation requires any business that discloses a customer's personal information (as defined by the Act) to any 3rd-party, for direct marketing purposes, to provide the customer a method for obtaining the names, addresses and certain other specified details of anyone who might have received that personal information. If you are a California resident you may request this information from SFTRAVEL, by writing to:

**SFTRAVEL, LLC**

848 N. Rainbow Blvd., #3333

Las Vegas, NV 89107 

**Attn: California Privacy Rights**

or by sending a message, with California Privacy Rights in the Subject line, [to this support form](http://sftravel.com/blog/contact-us) . SFTRAVEL is not obligated to respond to more than one such request from you per calendar year. 

**_XVII. Section Titles_**

The section titles used in these Policies are purely for convenience and carry with them no legal or contractual effect.

**_XVIII. What is the Effective Date of These Policies?_**

**This Policy was last updated on January 10, 2011.**
